So let's continue and city server that sea.
And here, let's include S&P time sink.
And now let's go down and register a new urine handler.
And we'll start by copying this one.
And let's update the comment to local time.
And update the structure to local time.
And the euro right here is local time Dutch Jason.
And the method is HTP get.
And then update the handler to get local time.
Just like this.
And then let's pass the name.
To register the handler.
Right now, let's go to find it up here.
And I'll start by copying this comment.
Then here, I'll change it to local time.
And I'll say here response.
By sending the local time.
OK, now let's go grab the function name.
And then go back.
And then right, static espérer type of function name.
And it's HD DVD request type.
Pointer RFQ.
And then we'll first ISP plug.
Good time, Jason requested.
And now we need to care local time, Jason.
100 byte buffer.
And set it to zero and then say if it will define a global variable later that will use here to check
at the time was set and we'll call it Gee Underscore, is local time set?
And if it is set, then he will update the JSON with the local time and use as print f into local time
JSON.
And we'll do the time here.
And then we'll get the time using our get time function.
And that's S&P time sync.
Now, let's get the response type.
For the request.
As application JSON.
The next httpd response, send.
Or the request from the buffer.
But the Starlin of the local time, Jason.
And then let's return.
ESP, OK.
OK, so now let's create this global variable.
So let's go up.
And make a comment here.
Local time status.
And it's a static bull.
Instead, it's a false.
And now let's get a case for it.
And we can use this one.
And change it to.
Change it to time service initialized.
Now, let's update the message as well.
And then change this global variable to global is local time set.
And then here we said at the true.
All right, so now let's go to Wi-Fi Bridge.
Because here I want to create a callback function so that the S&P time sync tasks start function can
be called via a custom callback.
And this will be called when the ESP 32 has an IP address.
So instead of explicitly calling it buried somewhere in the code, we can do it from men and you'll
see how this works once we're done.
So first here, let's comment.
Callback, typedef.
And it's typedef.
Void.
Wi-Fi connected.
Event back.
Underscore team.
And it's void.
All right, so this creates a type named Wi-Fi connected event called back underscore T for a pointer
to a function that takes no arguments and returns nothing.
OK, so now let's go to the bottom of the file.
And create a prototype.
Which sets the callback function.
And it's a void.
Wi-Fi app set callback.
And it takes the wi fi connected.
Event call back.
KB.
OK, now let's create another prototype that calls the callback function.
And it'll be a void Wi-Fi app.
Call callback.
And it's void.
OK, now let's go to find these two.
But first, let's go to the top.
And to you, let's write a comment.
Why fi application call back?
And it's static.
WI fi connected event callback.
And call it Wi-Fi connected event.
CB.
All right, looks good, so let's go down to the bottom for the public functions are.
And let's define them here.
And for the set callback.
Well, just set our Wi-Fi connected event CB.
To the callback passed to the function, and that's just cbrm.
That's it.
OK, so next, let's go to find this one.
And here we'll just call it a callback.
Like so.
Now, let's go up to the gut IP case.
And let's first comment check for connection callback.
And say if Wi-Fi connected event call back.
Then call wi fi app.
Call Colbeck.
All right, so if the callback is set, then we call the callback.
OK, so let's go to main that see.
And first, let's include.
ESB log.
And then let's also include.
S&P time sink.
And then here.
It will create a tag.
And call it men.
And next will create a callback as void Wi-Fi application, connected events.
And it's void.
And then here, will ESB log.
Why fi application connected?
And then now we can call S&P Time Sink.
Tests start.
And let's proceed by setting this function as a callback.
So copy it.
The down here will set connected event callback.
Using our wi fi app.
Said Caldbeck.
In pass, a reference to the function name.
And that's it.
So let's build.
The nut flesh.
Then open a monitor.
And then connect to the ESPN.
And go to the Web page with Graham.
Now, connect the ESP.
And let's see.
Nice, the local time is already displayed, that's great.
And the monitor shows the message from men.
And all the expected messages that follow.
So let's do some more programming in the next lesson.